Guide to the Emily Boardman estate papers, 1888-1903.
Boardman, Emily estate papers, 1888-1903.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Emily Boardman estate papers, 1888-1903.
1936
Emily Boardman, d.1898.
82 items.
A will, accounts, receipts, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Will, accounts, receipts, and correspondence of Emily Boardman, addressed to George R. Williams pertaining to the settlement of her estate.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Emily Boardman, of Trumansburg, New York, was a sister of Douglass Boardman, an Ithaca, New York lawyer.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Will, accounts, receipts, and correspondence of Emily Boardman, addressed to George R. Williams pertaining to the settlement of her estate.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Boardman, Emily, d.1898.; Williams, George R.
Places:
Trumansburg (N.Y.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Accounts.; Wills.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Will of Emily Boardman of Trumansburg, New York. Heirs named in will are: sisters Maria Sears, Delia Hathaway, Patty Spence, Gertrude Markham, Lucy B. Smith; brothers Russell Boardman, Harry Boardman, Truman Boardman, Douglass Boardman; nephew George H. Smith; and niece Ellen D. Williams., Nov. 17, 1888 (Folder 1)
- Copy of contract for payment of the Lewis Investment Co. bonds by Emily Boardman to Cornell University., Dec. 5, 1896 (Folder 1)
- Warranty Deed between the heirs of J.B. Williams and Charles Thomas of Ithaca, N.Y. seeling to Thomas land located in the town of Ithaca. The heirs are Mrs. May H. Williams, George R. Williams and Ellen B. his wife, Roger B. Williams and Caroline R. his wife, Henry S. Williams and Harriet H. his wife, Augusta H. Williams, Charlotte E. Williams, Mrs. Jane W. Newman and Jared T. her husband, Ella S. Williams, Clara M. Williams, Otis L. Williams, all of Ithaca, New York., Feb. 10, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Account of the Emily Boardman estate., Apr. 25, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Three (3) legal documents stating that George R. Williams of Ithaca, New York is the executor of the Emily Boardman estate., July 11, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Investments showing change of the Emily Boardman estate since the last statement., Sept. 22, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Tompkins Co., N.Y. Copy of the Appraiser's report on the estate of Emily Boardman., Oct. 8, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Legal document accepting the appraiser's report on the estate of Emily Boardman., Oct. 22, 1898 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Miss Frances Boardman of Los Angeles, Calif. to George R. Williams concerning the death of her father and the settlement of the Emily Boardman estate., Feb. 8, 1900 (1901?) (Folder 1)
- Fifty-eight (58) receipts to George R. Williams, as executor of the Emily Boardman estate, for dividend No. 2 on her estate. Signed by members of the Boardman, Sears, Spence, and Hathaway families, and numerous others., Feb. 1, 1901 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Miss Frances Boardman to George R. Williams concerning the payment of a draft Williams sent her., Feb. 27, 1901 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Theodore Spence of Starkey, N.Y. to George R. Williams concerning the settlement of the Riley Spence estate., Apr. (?) 23, 1902 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Mrs. Emma G. Myrick of Palmyra, Iowa to George R. Williams concerning the payment to her of her share of the Emily Boardman estate., Nov. 5, 1902 (Folder 1)
- Letter from C.M. Masters of Sparta, Wis. to George R. Williams concerning the death of Maria S. Blakeslee and settlement of the Emily Boardman estate., Feb. 24, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Mrs. C. Blakeslee of St. Augustine, Florida to George R. Williams concerning Frances Boardman, an heir of Emily Boardman., Mar. 8, 1903 (?) (Folder 1)
- Letter from C.M. Masters of Sparta, Wis. to George R. Williams concerning the settlement of the Emily Boardman estate., July 28, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Letter from C.M. Masters to George R. Williams concerning the settlement of the Emily Boardman estate., Nov. 5, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Statement of account of estate of Emily Boardman., Dec. 1, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Letter from C.M. Masters of Sparta, Wis. to George R. Williams concerning the settlement of the Maria S. Blakeslee and Emily Boardman estates., Dec. 4, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Grace H. Thian of Minneapolis, Minnesota to George R. Williams giving him the addresses of two relatives of Emily Boardman., Dec. 11, 1903 (Folder 1)
- Letter from Theodore Spence of Dundee, N.Y. to George R. Williams giving him the addresses of several members of the Spence family., Dec. 14, 1903 (Folder 1)